Guide to the John W. Shenk Papers, 1900-1935
Department of Special Collections
- CORRESPONDENCE
  - S - GENERAL IN (I). (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - SHENK, JOHN WESLEY (1875 - 19), including letters to the following persons:
      - Unidentified., (6) (Box 8, Folder 4)
        - - H - (Box 9, Folder 7)
          - Hoff, Mrs. Anna C., '20
          - Hoffmann, John W., '32-'33; (3)
          - Holabird, W. H., '13
          - Holland, W. H., '26
          - Hollingsworth, A. W., '27-'31; (3)
          - Hollzer, Harry A., '31
          - Holohan, James B., '31; (2)
          - Hood, Van Lee., '31
          - Hooper, George A., '31
          - Hoover, Herbert Jr., '30
          - Horn, John S., '23
          - Hoss, Herman H., '35
          - Hotel del Coronado., '27
          - Hotel del Monte., '31
          - Hotel Senator., '29; (2)
          - Houser, Frederick W., '24-'32; (3)
          - Huber, J., '13
          - Huddle, J. K., '26
          - Huff, C. C., '20
          - Huff, D. Eyman., '23
          - Hughes, Ralph L., '31
          - Huguley, J. B., '26
          - Huguley, Margaret T., '27-'29; (4)
          - Hultman, Frank T., '24
          - Hunter, Ben S., '24
          - Huntsberger, Glenn E., '27
          - Huntsberger, I. N., '13
          - Hupert, Mrs. C., '23
          - Hurin, James H., '08
          - Hutchins, C. F., '20
        - - I - (Box 9, Folder 8)
          - Iglesias, Santiago., '33
          - Imperial County, California.
            - Assessor., '30
            - Auditor., '22
            - Clerk., '23; (4)
            - Recorder., '08
            - Tax Collector., nd, '08-'26
          - Imperial County Irrigation District., '20
          - Imperial Valley Abstract, Title and Trust Company., '08; (2)
          - Imperial Water Company No. 1., '08
          - Inglis, Cecilia., '24
          - Ingraham, Everett L., '36; (3)
          - IRELAND, ESTATE OF., '24-'25; (7) (Box 9, Folder 9)
          - Irving, James., '13
          - Island Villa., '20
        - - J - (Box 9, Folder 10)
          - Jacks, Lile T., '31
          - James, Floyd R., '26-'28
          - James, Henry N., '26
          - James, William P., '08-'31; (4)
          - Jameson, H. G., '25
          - Janss, Peter., '22
          - Jeffries, William P., '26
          - Jennings, H. C., '15
          - Jewell, A. C., '33
          - Johnson, Hiram W., '11-'36; (10)
          - Johnston, Charles H., '24
          - Johnston, J. J., '24
          - Johnstone, W. A., '27
          - Jonathan Club., nd, '22-'32; (13)
          - Jones, Carl Power., '35; (3)
          - Jones, Frances., '33-'35
          - Jones, Griffith., '24-'26; (4)
          - Jones, Jonah Jr., '24
          - Jones, Mattison B., '13-'24
          - Jones, Mrs. Sallie M., '32
          - Jordan, Frank C., '24-'31; (8)
          - Judd, Albert Jr., '30
          - Judd, Mrs. Albert E., '30
          - JUDICIAL COUNCIL., '25-'32; (18) (Box 9, Folder 11)
          - Judson, Mrs. F. L., '07
          - Junior Chamber Of Commerce., '27
        - - K - (Box 9, Folder 12)
          - Kalt, E. E. R., '30
          - Kappa Sigma., '26
          - Kathan, Reid A., '25
          - Keetch, Arthur., '29
          - Keller, Anna P., '22
          - Kennedy, Vincent., '29-'30; (4)
          - Kenny, L. E., nd
          - Kerr, William M., '24-'32; (4)
            See also Los Angeles, City Of. Registrar of Voters.
          - Keyes, Asa., '26
          - Kidd, Herbert W., '24
          - Kiesling, Henry., '24-'25
          - Kiggens, Harold S., '24
          - King, F. W., '13
          - Kingham Funeral Company., nd
          - Kirby, Benjamin., '25
          - Kirby, E. N., '22
          - Kirby, Jess., '35
          - Kjellgren, Eric H., '26
          - Kincaid, Clarence L., '34
          - Kleinsmid, R. B. von., '30
          - Kling, David G., '27-'33
          - Knowland, Joseph R., '27
          - Koebig, A. H., '24-'26
          - Koerner, M., '20
          - Kohler, Mrs. Jean Fuller., '22
          - Kruse, Fred H., '32
        - - L - (Box 9, Folder 13)
          - Lampton, L. E., '23-'32; (3)
          - Langdon, W. H., '23
          - Langthorne, Gertrude., '24
          - LaPlante, William., '31
          - LaTourrette, Clinton., '32
          - Launcher, Charles R., '24
          - Launder, William H., '23
          - Lavine, Morris., '24-'26; (7)
          - Lawler, Oscar., '19
          - Lawyers' Club., '32
          - Lawyers Cooperative Publishing Company., '34-'35; (3)
          - Learned, Leslie E., '27
          - Lee, R.V.H., '27
          - Leeds, Walter R., '26
          - Lees, Anna C., '25; (2)
          - Legerton, Curtis C., '24; (2)
          - Lehman, Joseph A., '22
          - Leigh, Randolph., '23
          - Lemmon, Dal M., '32
          - Lennon, Mrs. Thomas J., '26
          - Lewis, John V., '33
          - Lincoln Club., '28-'34
          - Lincoln Mortgage Company., '25
          - Lindenbaum, Isidore., '33
          - Lindsay, Alexander., '26; (2)
          - Linhares, John., '22; (2)
          - Linn, Roy A., '31
          - Lippincott, J. B., '27
          - Lissner, Meyer., '23
          - Lister, Henry B., '28
          - Literary Digest., '25
          - Literary Guild Of America, Inc., '32-'33; (4)
          - Little, Walter J., '27-'29
          - Littler, Robert., '28
          - Lobdell, J. Carl., '23
          - Lochlin, C. B., '31
          - Locke, Charles Edward., '32
          - Loewenthal, Max., '24
          - Logan, Charles L., '30
            See also Los Angeles, County Of. Recorder.
          - Logan, William., '24
          - Logie, John H., '22; (2)
          - Lones, C. E., '23
          - Long, Oscar Fitzalan., '23
          - Long Beach Bar Association.
          - Long Beach Press., '20
          - Lorenz, W. H., '28
          - Los Altos Golf and Country Club., '30; (2)
          - Los Angeles, City Of.
            - Assessor., '07
            - Board Of Library Directors., '11
            - Board Of Public Works., '10; (4)
            - [Board Of Public Service Commissioners]., '11
            - Bureau Of Power and Light., '23
            - City Council., '12
            - Crime Commission., '23; (2)
            - Metropolitan Water District., '34
            - Registrar Of Voters., '32-'33; (4)
          - Los Angeles, County Of.
            - Board Of Supervisors., '24; (2)
            - Recorder., '24
            - Sheriff., nd, '34; (2)
            - Superior Courts., nd
            - Tax Collector., '27-'28
          - Los Angeles, Municipal League Of., '24
          - Los Angeles Bar Association.
          - Los Angeles Central Labor Council., '32
          - Los Angeles Sewing Machine Company., '08
          - Lowe, Titus., '20-'31; (3)
          - Lund, Agnes., '31
          - Luter, John W., '27-'32; (3)
          - Lyman, Clarence A., '22
          - Lyman, Edward D., '34-'35
          - Lynch, Robert Newton., '26
          - Lyon, Charles W., '23-'27
          - Lyons, Harry., '27
        - - M - (Box 9, Folder 14)
          - McAdoo, Alfred H., '24-'33
          - MCADOO, WILLIAM GIBBS., '32-'35; (8) (Box 9, Folder 15)
          - McCandless, F. C., '26
          - McCarthy, Neil S., '30
          - McComas, Fred V., '27
          - McCormick, A. I., '20
          - McCormick, Paul J., '24
          - McCray, C. H., '25; (2)
          - McCulloch, Charles E., '29-'31; (3)
          - McDill, George W., '27-'30
          - MacDonald, Frank A., '24
          - McDonald, George W., '24; (2)
          - McEntire, Walter F., '24
          - mcEverlast, Inc., '29
          - McGovern, T. J., '27
          - McGrath, J. J., '33-'34; (3)
          - McGroarty, John S., '24
          - McInerney, Joseph., '27
          - McKevitt, Hugh K., '25
          - McKinley, J. W., '27
          - McKinstry, Laura M., '27
          - McKisick, R. T., '24
          - Macklin, Robert K., '26; (2)
          - McLucas, Victor R., '31-'32
          - McMillan, J. W., '07
          - McMonigal, Mr. and Mrs. H. E., '29
          - McNab, John L., '28-'31
          - McNaught's Magazine., '25
          - McNoble, George F., '25-'30
          - McPherrin, Paul H., '31
          - McPherrin, Roy D., '08-'33
          - McPike, H. H., '33
          - MCRAE, FRED W. (brother-in-law of JWS), '22-'34; (16) (Box 9, Folder 16)
          - MCRAE, SUSAN. (sister of JWS), '26-'31; (5) (Box 9, Folder 17)
          - McVey, W. E., '08
          - McWilliams, Mr. and Mrs. Robert L., '31-'32
          - Mader, C. P., '33
          - Mallard, Walter., '07-'13
            See also Los Angeles, City Of. Assessor.
          - Mallon & Vordenberg., '08
          - Maltman, John S., '23
          - Marchant, Thomas W., '32
          - Marengo Water Company., '22
          - Marr, Ned., '34
          - Marriott, Francis M. Jr., '22
          - Robert Marsh & Co., '06
          - Marshall, George A., '22
          - Martin, Austin O., '24
          - Martin, James R., '30
          - Martin, Theodore., '24
          - Marvin, Mrs. William G., '32
          - Masujima, Rokuichiro., '22
          - Matheson, Duncan., '30
          - Matheson, J. L., '24
          - Mathews, W. B., nd, '25-'30; (6)
          - Matson Navigation Company., '32
          - Matthews, Charles., '31
          - Matthews & Matthews., '13; (2)
          - MATTOON, EVERETT W., '26-'35; (7)
          - May, Carl L., '24
          - Mayer, Louis B., '31
          - Meikle, R. V., '22
          - Frank Meline Company., '32
          - Mendocino County Bar Association.
          - Merced County, California. County Recorder., '20
          - Merchants Trust Company., '08
          - Merrill, A.E., '10-'13
          - Mesmer, Joseph., '30
          - Methodist Episcopal Church. Southern California Annual Conference., '28-'31
          - Michigan, University Of. Registrar., '07
          - Middleton, Bessie B., '24
          - Miller, Hattie M., '23
          - Miller, Justin., '28
          - Miller, Kenton A., '23-'33; (6)
          - Millikan, C. E., '27
          - Millspaugh, Jesse F., '13
          - Minchin, Michael., '24
          - Mines, William W., '24-'33; (4)
          - Mitchell, William D., '29-'30; (4)
          - Mohr, Andrew., '13
          - Mohr, W. H., '24
          - Monnette, Orra E., '13-'24
          - Monroe, Charles., '26
          - Montgomery, S., '19
          - Montgomery, T. M., '26
          - Moore, Albert M., '13
          - Moore, Minor., '24-'31
          - Moran and McWhinnie., '22
          - Morgan,., '26
          - Morgan, W. B., '09
          - Morrish, Will F., '25
          - Morrison, Fred W., '33
          - Morrison, J. A., '07
          - Morrison, S., '22
          - Morse, Wayne L., '33
          - Morse, William M. Jr., '24
          - Mott, John G., '10-'35; (3)
          - Mould, Thomas R., '20
          - Moxey, R. B., '32
          - Mueller, Oscar., '30
          - Muhleman, Frank L., '24
          - Mulligan, H. A., '33
          - Mulqueeney, P. C., '23
          - Munson, A. C., '30-'31
          - Murray, John., '09
          - Murray, Stanley., '24
          - Mutual Business Club., '31
          - Myers, Blanche., '33; (2)
          - MYERS, LOUIS., '24-'34; (28) (Box 9, Folder 19)
        - - N - (Box 9, Folder 20)
          - Nair, Thomas L., '26
          - Nash, Paul M., '31; (2)
          - Nathan, Milton A., '24
          - Nathan-Dohrmann Company., '32
          - National Economic League., '28-'30
          - National Encyclopedia Of American Biography., '24
          - National Geographic Magazine., '24-'33; (3)
          - Nelson, Dario H., '28-'31; (5)
          - Nelson, N. B.
          - Netherton, J. C., '24
          - Neumiller, C. L., '28
          - Nevada. Supreme Court., '31
          - New Process Company., '25
          - New York Life Insurance Company., '08-'33; (3)
          - Newby, Nathan., '13-'23
          - Newcomb, M., '21
          - Newell, R. A., '26
          - Newerf, William D., '25
          - Newlin, Gurney E., '26-'28
          - Newlin & Ashburn., '24
          - Newman, Frank J., '32-'33; (4)
          - Newman, Marjorie Hines., '23
          - Nichols, Alan., '26-'28; (4)
          - Nichols, Ernest E., '25
          - Nichols, James C., '24; (2)
          - Niendorff, John H., '30
          - Nolan, Joseph F., '26-'31; (3)
          - Noon, Mark E.
            See California, State Of. Board Of Prison Directors.
          - Normandie Hotel., '34
          - Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Co., '23-'28; (6)
          - Nourse, J. R., '13
        - - O - (Box 10, Folder 1)
          - Oakland, Port Of., '30
          - O'Brien, Clarence A., '32
          - Occidental Life Insurance Company., '29; (2)
          - Ocheltree, G. B., '24
          - O'Connor, J. Robert., '27
          - O'Connor & Havill., '28
          - OHIO WESLEYAN UNIVERSITY., nd, '27-'34; (48) (Box 10)
          - Olmsted, J. Emmett., '30
          - O'Melveny, Henry W., '31
          - O'Melveny, Stuart., '24
          - O'Melveny, Tuller & Myers., '32
          - Oneal, Louis., '34
          - Oneonta Club., '24-'29
          - Oneonta Transfer Company., '25
          - Oram, Gordon E., '30
          - Orcutt, Mrs. D. Sybil., '07-'08
          - Oregon, University Of., '29
          - Ormsby, E. S., '13
          - Osborne, H. Z., nd
          - Oster, Frank F., '31
          - Otto, John., '24
          - Otto, Paul J., '24-'25
          - Overton, Eugene., '27
          - Owen, Erwin W., '25
          - Owen, Wilhelmina., '22
          - Owens, Timon E., '31
          - Oxnam, G. Bromley., '25
        - - P - (Box 10, Folder 3)
          - Pace, Troy., '30-'34; (3)
          - Pacific American Oil Company., '24-'31; (3)
          - Pacific Gas and Electric Company., '28-'33; (6)
          - Pacific Southwest Trust and Savings Bank., '24; (2)
          - Padan, Franklin., '27
          - Page, Benjamin E., '25
          - Palmer, William Fleet., '30
          - Palmer, William J., '31
          - Papock, Herman., '30
          - Parker, Robert S., '22-'23
          - Parmele, G. H.
          - Parmelee, Z. L., '25
          - Parmelee, Mrs. Z. L., '20
          - Parr, Fred. D., '34
          - Pasadena Bar Association., '22
          - Passafiume, Joseph., '22
          - Paulist Fathers., '29
          - Peace Officers Association Of California., '30
          - Peart, Hartley F., '34; (2)
          - Peck, C. E., '07
          - Peck, Earl Curtis., nd
          - Peck, James E., '08; (5)
          - Peoples Abstract Title and Trust Co., '08
          - Perkins, Voltaire., '27
          - Pernau-Walsh Printing Co., '24
          - Persons, V. S., '22
          - Petermichael, J. J., '27
          - Peters, '27
          - Petersen, Maud E., '31
          - Pfaffinger, Frank X., '25
          - Phelps, W. W., '27
          - Phi Delta Phi., '32
          - Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance Company., '12-'15; (3)
          - Pike, Warren A., '25
          - Pioneer Abstract and Title Guaranty Co., '07
          - Piper, C. E., '22-'30
          - Pitzer, Sloan., '24; (2)
          - Plummer, J. A., '35; (3)
          - Pomona College., '29
          - Pond, John E., '26-'28; (3)
          - Pontius, D. W., '30
          - Pope, James H., '20-'23
          - Porter, Charles R., '28
          - Edward J. Power Company, Inc., '25-'26
          - Preston School Of Industry., '23; (2)
          - Prewitt, Mrs. E. R., '07
          - Priaulx, Percy J., '13
          - Pridham, J. C., '08-'23
          - Pritchard, George A., '20-'26
          - Proctor, William H., '29
          - Pruitt, Drew., '13
          - Pullen, John F., '34; (2)
          - Purcell, G. W., '07
        - - Q - (Box 10, Folder 4)
          - Quillian, Fletcher., '24
        - - R - (Box 10, Folder 5)
          - Rainey, Edward., '27
          - Ralston, Jackson H., '31
          - Randall, L. B., '24
          - Rapp, Vermell., '13
          - Rapp & Company, Inc., '27
          - Rasmus, Henry I., '29
          - Recorder Printing and Publisher Company., '31
          - Redding, Mary F., '25
          - Redwine, H. G., '24-'32
          - Reeve, Sidney N., '21-'24; (3)
          - Reid, Mont J., '20-'29
          - Reppy, Roy V., '24
          - Reynolds, William M., '22
          - Rhea, Hannah S. G., '24
          - Rheinstorm, Beatrice B., '24-'27
          - Rhoades, James M., nd, '22
          - Richards, Don W., '31-'32
          - Richards, John P., '31
          - Richards, R. D., '20
          - Richardson, Bonner., '27
          - RICHARDSON, FRIEND W., nd, '23-'26; (14) (Box 10, Folder 6)
          - Richardson, Howell W., '27
          - Riddle, Lester C., '29-'31; (3)
          - Ridgway, Thomas C., '26-'34; (8) (Box 10, Folder 7)
          - Riege, Charles H., '24
          - Riggins, Harley E., '25
          - Ringo, Richard G., '31
          - Rives, James C., '22
          - Roberts, Caesar A., '27-'31
          - Roberts, W. A., '13
          - Robertson, Mr. and Mrs. Howard., '31
          - Robinson, Dudley., '24-'28
          - Robinson, Edgar Eugene., '25
          - Robinson, Faith., nd
          - Robinson, Mrs. George O., '23
          - Robinson, L. G., '28
          - Robinson, S. B., '31
          - Robinson, Thomas W., '07-'24
          - Robinson, William L., '32
          - Robson, Kernan., '28; (3)
          - Rochester, George W., '33
          - Rockafellor, J. E., '24
          - Roller, P. F., '22-'33; (4)
          - ROLPH, JAMES JR., '28-'33; (15) (Box 10, Folder 8)
          - Roosevelt, Franklin D., '32-'33; (3)
          - Roosevelt Progressive Republican League., '12
          - Rosenkranz, Elias V., '29
          - Ross, John Stewart., '27
          - Rossi, Angelo J., '31
          - Rothacker-Aller Laboratories, Inc., '22
          - Rubin, I. R., '30
          - Ruoff, Hermann F., '21-'25; (3)
          - Rush, W. S., '07
          - Russill, Louis P., '24
          - A. J. Rutledge & Sons., '23
          - Rutledge, Frank., '24-'26; (3)
        - - S - (Box 10, Folder 9)
          - Sacramento Bee., '32
          - Sadicoff, Harry G., '27
          - St. Ignatius College., '30
          - Salinger, Victor R., '26-'31
          - Sample, Ed. P., '23
          - Sandborn, Mrs. A. R., '27
          - San Francisco Advertising Club., '32
          - San Francisco Bar Association.
          - San Francisco Chronicle., '27
          - San Francisco, University Of. Law School., '35
          - San Gabriel Valley Country Club., nd, '07; (2)
          - San Jose Abstract and Title Insurance Company., '27
          - Sanaker, Otto., '25
          - Santa Clara, California. Recorder., '28
          - Tax Collector., '27-'30
          - Santa Clara County Bar Association.
          - Santa Clara University., '31
          - Sargent, John G., '27; (3)
          - Saturday Night., '27
          - Schauer, R. Rey., '27
          - Scheinman, B. J., '27
          - Schenck, Joseph., '26
          - Schmidt, Ruben S., '24
          - Schmittou, C. V., '30
          - Schnepfe, Fred E., '29
          - Schrader, F. von., '32
          - Schroeder, H. N., '31
          - Schultz, Carl., '13
          - Schultz, Edward F., '24-'31; (4)
          - Schwabacher-Frey Stationery Co., '29
          - Schweitzer, Dell A., '26-'33
          - Scofield, Jerome V., '29
          - Scott, Joseph., '24
          - Scott, Robert H., '26
          - Scripps College., '28
          - Seager, Howard W., '24-'31; (4)
          - Sears, Charles., '27; (2)
          - Seawell, Emmet., '31
          - SECURITY FIRST NATIONAL BANK., '22-'32; (17) (Box 10, Folder 10)
          - Seiter, Orville R., '29
          - Seymour, Joseph F., '34
          - SHANK, EDMOND. (brother of JWS), '07-'35; (47) (Box 10, Folder 11)
          - Sharkey, Will R., '24
          - Shaw, Charles H., '30
          - Shaw, Frank L., '33
          - Shaw, Lucien., '29
          - Shaw, Victor E., nd, '08-'13; (3)
          - Shaw, Warwick A., '07-'08
          - Shelby, Mrs. Charles H., '22
          - Shelby, Mrs. J., '23
          - Sheldon, Charles H., '31
          - SHENK, ADOLPHUS. (brother of JWS), '06-'35; (138) (Box 10, Folder 12)
          - SHENK, JOHN W. SR. (father of JWS), '07-'20; (13) (Box 10, Folder 13)
          - SHENK, Joyce. (niece of JWS), '27
          - Shenk, Lenah. (wife of JWS), '31
          - SHENK, SUSANNA C. (mother of JWS), '24-'26; (6) (Box 10, Folder 14)
          - SHENK, WILLIAM W. (brother of JWS), '06-'33; (29) (Box 10, Folder 15)
          - Sherry, Henry., '13
          - Shields, Peter., '29
          - Shienman, Benjamin J., '27
          - Shontz, Orfa Jean., '33
          - Shortridge, Samuel M., '20-'31; (10)
          - Shurtleff, Charles A., '34
          - Silver Shield Service, Inc., '22; (3)
          - Silverberg, M. B.
            See Los Angeles, City of. Crime Commission.
          - Simon, Ernest R., '27
          - Simons, Seward S., '13
          - Skagit County, Washington. Treasurer., '30-'32; (3)
          - Skirvin, C. F., '29
          - Sloane, W. &. J., '35
          - Sloane, William A., '24-'29; (4)
          - Smallwood, Claude., '26
          - Smith, Clyde W., '25
          - Smith, Dave F., nd, '33
          - Smith, Mrs. Eldora., '07; (3)
          - Smith, Frank J., '25
          - Smith, Frank M., '33-'34
          - Smith, Mrs. H. O., '30
          - Smith, Leslie., '26
          - Smith, Mrs. S. C., '32
          - Smith, Willard P., '24
          - Snider, W. J., '23
          - Snider Brothers., '23-'25; (6)
          - Snyder, W. Cloyd., '29-'34; (4)
          - Socha, Max E., '32
          - Solomon, Fred H., '29
          - Solomon, Irl., '26; (2)
          - Sonoma County Bar Association.
          - South Pasadena, City Of. Water Dept., '32
          - South Pasadena Lodge No. 367. F.&A.M., '07-'22
          - Southern California, University of., '34
          - Southern California Edison Company., '24
          - Southern California Gas Company., nd
          - Southern California Law Review., '28
          - Southern Pacific Company., '27
          - Speik, Frederick A., '25-'34; (3)
          - Spencer, Fannie Bixby., '23
          - Spicer, Charles W., '30
          - Sproul, Joseph P., '27; (2)
          - Sproul, Robert G., '29
          - Stafford, H. M., '34
          - Standard Oil Company., '30-'34; (3)
          - Stanford University.
            - Board Of Athletic Control., '33
            - Dean Of Women. Yost, Mary., nd,'26-'33; (6)
            - Registrar., '29-'35; (5)
          - Stanley, Welles K., '08-'22
          - Stanley-DeBlois Company., '08; (2)
          - Stanton, Robert H., '34
          - Stassforth, Edna., '07
          - Stathis, Harry., '30
          - Steckel, George., '24
          - Steele, John P., '24
          - Steiger, George J., '31
          - Steiner, Fred A., '32
          - Stephens, Albert Lee., '26-'35; (8)
          - Stephenson Company. Clerk., '22
          - Sterry, Philip C., '27
          - Stevens, W. L., '27
          - Stewart, Fred E., '33
          - Stewart, H. S. A. Jr., '31
          - Stillwell, J. E., '30-'33; (3)
          - Stimson, Marshall., '30
          - Stoermer, Grace S., '32
          - Stone, C. W., '26
          - Stone, Duke., nd
          - Stone, Harlan Fiske., '24
          - Strait, George S., '24-'26; (3)
          - Strother, S. L., '33
          - Stuart, Edward A., '31
          - Sullivan, Jeremiah F., '27
          - Sullivan, Stephen L., '13
          - Surr, Howard., '33
          - Susman, Leo H., '25
          - Sutherland, George., '29
          - Sutton, Ernest V., '20-'31; (3)
          - Sutton, Mrs. Ernest V., '26
          - Swaffield, Roland G., '24
          - Sweaza, Charles G., '24
          - Sweet, Joe G., '30
        - - T - (Box 10, Folder 16)
          - Taft, Fred H., '24-'30; (3)